{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Stove Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40250/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40250,"taskName":"Gas, Pellet, or Wood Stove - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Gas, Pellet, or Wood Stove","xmTaskDescriptor":"Stove Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":303,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Fix Gas Stove Wood stoves","textMessagingName":"Repr Woodstove","rolloverLongDesc":"Handle repairs, maintenance, troubleshooting for fireplace units, gas log sets, pellet stoves \u0026 wood stoves. May only service certain brands.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes wood, gas \u0026 pellet fueled systems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Gas, Pellet, or Wood Stove.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Stove Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Pellet, Gas, Wood Stove","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":31,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Gas Pellet or Wood Stove Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Gas, Pellet, or Wood Stove - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Gas or Pellet Stove Project","urlName":"Gas-Pellet-or-Wood-Stove-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Stove Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Pellet, Gas, Wood Stove Repairs","searchKeywords":"Fix,Gas,Stove,Wood,stoves,burning,fireplace,vent,direct,iron,cast,Maintenance,barbeque,radiance,outside,outdoor,heating,heat,cooking,fireplaces,pellets,cook,ventless,vented,free,soapstone,grill,Pellet","emcCategoryOid":-12031,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":557,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40250/":{"taskOID":40250,"originalTaskOID":40250,"setID":557,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5677,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Unit","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of unit do you want to repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7059,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood burning","answerDisplayText":"Wood burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4634,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pellet burning","answerDisplayText":"Pellet burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4343,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil burning","answerDisplayText":"Oil burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4028,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Natural gas burning","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4940,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Propane burning","answerDisplayText":"Propane burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2755,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gas logs","answerDisplayText":"Gas logs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4259,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the nature of the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4109,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Needs regular service","answerDisplayText":"Needs regular service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1197,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Burning too fast","answerDisplayText":"Burning too fast","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1971,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Does not produce enough heat (inefficient)","answerDisplayText":"Does not produce enough heat (inefficient)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4300,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not venting properly or creating too much smoke","answerDisplayText":"Not venting properly or creating too much smoke","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2811,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Glass is broken","answerDisplayText":"Glass is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4921,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Problem with fan","answerDisplayText":"Problem with fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4923,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Problem with switch or thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Problem with switch or thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4922,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Problem with remote control","answerDisplayText":"Problem with remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5677,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Unit","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of unit do you want to repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7059,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood burning","answerDisplayText":"Wood burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4634,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pellet burning","answerDisplayText":"Pellet burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4343,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil burning","answerDisplayText":"Oil burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4028,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Natural gas burning","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4940,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Propane burning","answerDisplayText":"Propane burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2755,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gas logs","answerDisplayText":"Gas logs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7059,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood burning","answerDisplayText":"Wood burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4634,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pellet burning","answerDisplayText":"Pellet burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4343,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil burning","answerDisplayText":"Oil burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4028,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Natural gas burning","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4940,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Propane burning","answerDisplayText":"Propane burning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2755,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gas logs","answerDisplayText":"Gas logs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4259,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the nature of the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4109,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Needs regular service","answerDisplayText":"Needs regular service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1197,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Burning too fast","answerDisplayText":"Burning too fast","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1971,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Does not produce enough heat (inefficient)","answerDisplayText":"Does not produce enough heat (inefficient)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4300,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not venting properly or creating too much smoke","answerDisplayText":"Not venting properly or creating too much smoke","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2811,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Glass is broken","answerDisplayText":"Glass is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4921,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Problem with fan","answerDisplayText":"Problem with fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4923,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Problem with switch or thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Problem with switch or thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4922,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Problem with remote control","answerDisplayText":"Problem with remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4109,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Needs regular service","answerDisplayText":"Needs regular service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1197,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Burning too fast","answerDisplayText":"Burning too fast","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1971,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Does not produce enough heat (inefficient)","answerDisplayText":"Does not produce enough heat (inefficient)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4300,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not venting properly or creating too much smoke","answerDisplayText":"Not venting properly or creating too much smoke","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2811,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Glass is broken","answerDisplayText":"Glass is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4921,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Problem with fan","answerDisplayText":"Problem with fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4923,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Problem with switch or thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Problem with switch or thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4922,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Problem with remote control","answerDisplayText":"Problem with remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}